Hello friends, welcome to our
YouTube channel P4 Portfolio. Today we are going to
talk about ICICI Lombard
General Insurance. You must be aware that
a few days ago, news came that it is going to be
present with Indian General Insurance. So we will
discuss about that in detail as well and also
know whether after this merger, we can see this
ICICI Lombard becoming a
multi-barreled company in the long term or
not and whether this is the right time to
invest in it or not. We will
talk about that but before that, if you have
not subscribed to this channel, then please
subscribe and press the notification button to get regular updates.
Also, join the Telegram channel
whose link is given in the description box. So,
you can see that the
last date price of ICICI Lombard is ₹5, which is
seen down by 1.36 percent. If we
talk about the market, then the
market is around 5800. The period price is
25.2, the industry price is also 29.95, Suresh is
9.4  Talking about deliverables per cent,
we are seeing a strong of 56.87 here. If we
take a detailed information about the merger, then
life insurance custom from Indian Ek General Insurance Company,
Indian festival, the third largest, let's know in detail
what
is this news, so you can see that Indian Ek is a
non-life insurance subscription
arrangements of companies in a statement.
Financial details were not disclosed to
Indian Ek
General android 2017 road, so here it is
believed that a deal of 2018 crores is going to happen.
Best Dancer Chair Exchange Rate
Sun Commented by Independent Addiction
Accepted by the Respective WhatsApp
ICICI Lombard and Indian member
holders and Indian I will receive two years of
ICICI Lombard for every one in
fifty shades of Indian exam date on which the
scheme has been approved by the God, so here
this is not related to us because the
shares of Indian Ek are
not listed publicly, but those who have  Let the merger happen
on time. ICICI
Lombard shares are going to be acquired.
For this information, you can know that the venture
company will get necessary approvals. Non-life
insurance business will be merged from
Bharti Equity to ICICI Lombard. How will Bharti Equity's
life insurance business remain intact?
So, here you
should know that Bharti Equity has two businesses -
general insurance
and life insurance. So, the general
insurance business will remain intact here. The Bharti
Equity
life insurance business is going to remain intact.
Bharti Enterprises and
French Multinational Insurance will have 51
percent
stake respectively in Bharti Equity.
Special rights have been granted to Bharti Equity
and post-merger, Bharti Equity will be
categorized as public shareholders.
So, when the merger happens, neither of them is going to get any
extra privilege. They are
not going to get any special privilege here.
They are public.  Shareholding will be counted
for ad quarter dynasty 2114 from one
General Solvency and Minimum Capital
Requirement 1.7 There were regulatory
requirements for that means it
shows more than that It is a
good thing when combined graduate
student 11015 percent Chyol Ubud
HP Water Cycle Edit Legal Advisors So the
information given here is
not that much for us so I am
not going to read like this If you want to read this then you can
pause the video and read it If you want to
know about the views of the company then the
company said in a statement that the
proposed translation for profile
provider meaning of love for the native and
ICICI Lombard to consolidate
market leading position in the non-life
insurance sector becoming the third
largest non-life insurance amount by
Yadav market only 8.7 on pro forma basis
So here pro forma you
can understand that if this merger happens then  If
ICICI Lombard becomes the third largest
non-life insurance company, then the
market here will increase to 8.7
percent, which is a good thing for the company.
Bhargav Dasgupta,
MD and CEO of ICICI Lombard, has
said here that this is a landmark
joining of ICICI Lombard
and he is confident that the company is committed to the
value of creative prowess and we are
excited by its capabilities
and friends. Now Indian
tattoo and French, the company is a talent and
employment with strong cultural freedom
and will look forward to welcoming Mintu
to the ICICI Lombard family here.
Bhargav Dasgupta, MD of ICICI Lombard General Insurance, says that
every moment of life, the comments made by him are positive in many places.
Here, I am
talking about the Indian employees of the company, their employees are
very talented and there is a
strong cultural momentum here, so welcome to the
ICICI.  The Lombard family's commentary here
appears to be quite positive. Next, the
companies also said in a statement that the
proposed merger was expected to
result in value creation for all
stakeholders. Meaningful revenue and
operations in registered policyholders are also
expected to gain from more productive end-to-end
customer connect points. The
way of working here will improve slightly. Advanced
products will also be visible in the merger, but customer
connect with will also be seen
after this merger. Rakesh Bharti Mittal, Chairman
and Managing Director of Indian Equifax General Insurance and
DPA, said that
consistent
growth for productive partnerships and
increased distribution footprint is
significant, but he is confident that the
proposed combination of business with
ICICI Lombard will result in greater businesses
and create value for all stakeholders.
So, here we saw that the comments from the
MD and CEO of ICICI Lombard were
quite positive, and
here Indian Equifax  The comments from
Rakesh Bharti Mittal, Chairman of General Insurance, are
also
looking very positive here. We are
seeing consistent growth in their business.
Productive partnerships have been formed here, and
good committees are visible here. If we
talk about Bharti Enterprises, it is
not just looking to sell today. Bharti
Enterprises has been looking for a higher oil
general insurance company for the last 728
years. Bharti Enterprises has been
looking to find some friend or friend.
Here, Bharti Airtel was talking to Reliance,
but till now the deal was
not finalized here. So, we are
not going to waste much time here. Moving forward, let us
know what difference it would have made if Indian generals and admirals were proposed and joined together. So, since July 31, 2014,
General Idea market share was 1.4, first
denied sector-20 Dangra. This additional
premium of around Rs 810 crore is being done.
ICICI Lombard has a market
share of 7.7, General Insurance.  Sector
rebellion day dreaming of and it was
around force so here you will see how to
interest of winter non-life business net
and creams comment pressure solvency
profit after tax market syrup everything will be
seen here market plus
if this merger happens then ICICI
Lombard can be seen as the third largest company here in
which when combined with the
largest private non-life
insurance and the third largest in the general
insurance industry after New India
Assurance and United India Insurance but
here you can understand that we can
see a significant decline here, the
business of the company will grow if this merger is
successful, if this warrior
puja happens then the combined entry will be made the
largest private non-life insurance company and will also
become the largest
in the general insurance industry so
here the movie is looking quite good, it
shows a good positive till the closing or
proposed transaction is subject to
various conditions, pending
regulatory approval from the Insurance
Regulatory and Development  They will have to get some proposals from the
Competition Commission of India,
Securities and Exchange Board of India, that is,
ACB.
Here, there are regulatory approvals here.
Approval is required from the stock exchange here.
RBI, approval of
shareholders, ICICI Lombard and
Bhartiya Bank. It is
also very important to use cross here. 30 The Third
Merger Del Inter Insurance Sector
HDFC and some questions of LT General
Insurance in August 2017. Here,
HDFC and completed a question of
acquisition of Polar Mink Health Insurance
in January 21, 2014.
This type of place in the insurance sector
shows me positive patients here.
I will tell you in detail that
we have discussed here that you will become
stronger. Special Number was already a
very big player,
but if the merger is successful, then
we can see further growth here. So let's
also talk about at which level we should talk about it.
So you see.  We can see that we have come to the chart.
Here we see that
after the fall in March, a strong recovery is being
seen, but after that it was seen
moving in the same range. There has
not been much momentum seen in it.
If we talk about the current situation,
it is trading below its twenty-day
moving average of TDS. The
moving waves of Dahej are calculated and come at a
level around 1043 and currently the
closing seen is
around 1043. Let's talk about the indicators here. If we
talk about money products, then you will see that the
number of money plants is also gradually decreasing.
You can see it going towards 53k,
which is gradually visible to us here
in the middle. If we talk
about business, then the number of RS is
calculated and comes out as 2.78. Now we
will see that here also the special time
seems to be maintained. Let's also talk about MS Word,
so MSP.  At present,
you will see the Swiss roll there and
after this tower,
we have seen a significant decline. If we talk
about Bollinger Bands, you will
see that
after presenting resistance around the airport, the stock is
seeing a decline and is trading
near its lower point. The lower
back is 1512. The level around 11067
is the median. I have seen a level around one phase at more than 100. If we
talk about the pivot point, then the paper level
is calculated here. The
level around 1295. We will not talk about the resistance level
because currently the stock is
seeing a decline, so the support
we can expect is Banda Hussain. The
level around 2025. If it does not go beyond that, then the
level of 1187 is also visible here.
Now let's go one and a half inch more where
a candle will represent one month,
which will show what kind of moments and if you
make it, you will see that
we are not getting to see much old history here.  The
stock was listed at the end of 2017
and after that it has been making
explosive returns. After that, a
crush was seen in the market and the stock had
come down a lot but the
thing to note is that when it was listed,
this stock did not reach that level.
Today, the stock took support above 750
and we saw an immediate recovery
and you will see that for the last four months, the
stock has been seen trading in the same range. A
lot of momentum seems to be
decreasing here. A lot of slow
momentum is visible here. So
what should I do about the positions in such a situation? If
you have maintained a position at a very high level, then it is
my property, brother, the company is good, it is
not a loss-making company, so it should remain
here. If you have
maintained a position at a lower level, if you have
maintained a position here for the long term, then please
click on continue. But if you
create a short complaint, then there
is important support here. If that level breaks further, then further
decline can be seen. This is the
level near the strong point. If this level is
broken, then it is  If so, we
may see the decline becoming even more intense here. Now
friends, let's talk about the stock.
I believe the stock is good and
can become a multibagger and has also made a mark in the multi-brand retail sector.
In the last few years,
despite the merger, we have given a good forecast for the two-three years. But
we have told you that even
if the merger does not happen,
its
market share is still quite high, more than 70% of the service sector,
around 7.7%. If this
scheme is successful, you will see that we
can also see good growth here.
We have to see talent and employees
from both sides. This commentary is
coming out much better. So, I think
you can think about investing here
for the long term and if you have paid attention here, then you
never see much momentum. In 10-15 days, a
top is taken out in a range. If you are thinking that you will
see it here very soon, then it is
not so. It is a long term horse. If you want to
invest here for the long term, then whatever  If you are an
aggressive inverter,
activate it here. For them, I
would like to tell you the level which is from 1240 to
around 120. You can think about rumors there.
For the long term, I
believe that the stop has also consolidated at this level for a long time
and here the second day
's low also
comes as a support of points. So, if such ministers
can think about wine at this level,
but for those who want to wait and are
conservative in nature,
I will definitely
tell them the level which is more than 150 spice
labels will come there, you can think about it.
For the long term, this is my stuff, a
good stock for the long term. If you
forget about it, then it can
make you good profits in the long term. You can
think about giving it a place in your portal. And if you want to get your portfolio
reviewed by us, then
I have given it in the description box. So,
if you liked this video, then like,
share, comment, subscribe,
motivate me. Thank you. Stay happy,
happy investing.